{
    "id": "32323e2d25c3485292a64a7595581527",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The know the man ……………………….. filed the complaint.",
            "description": "Use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "981d3a33b83e443c928868097a9dbc3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the boy ………………………….. I was talking about.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses that can be used instead of whom.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c5a9ca52ca8840969dbb2a1f8c61fe4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a woman ………………………….. sells spices in the market.",
            "description": "Use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "405698ba50ca42eaa0becd3d7eb0ba30"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a question …………………………. no one could answer.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses, either which or that can refer to things, ideas etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "348a994931f245f1a3e8f23dceae8720"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plants ………………………….. I bought from the nursery last week have died.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "138ac0250a5345b1bd35daf7170556eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman ………………………… knee was broken required surgery.",
            "description": "The woman required surgery. Her knee was broken. We use whose in the place of possessive adjectives like his, her, their etc. The woman whose knee was broken required surgery.",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "13e720aea0ce4b7e92f8381edc018e9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ……………………….. parents had died now lives in an orphanage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who's",
                "whose",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "99079102362a4e7188ecff8482527859"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers ………………………….. were used to decorate the stage were not real.",
            "description": "Either that or which is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d07832730efe46b5adf928fcd557c4c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The parrot ………………………….. I have been keeping for a while can speak a few words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whom",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9cd3cb3ee554419eab34be641f307292"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ……………………………. have been selected for the team are practicing in the stadium.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c56acd5e544c4f56a009b96977f5646a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house …………………………..  I bought from my uncle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e1111b09afb142c1af24e32d45219c74"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man released the birds ………………………….. were kept in a cage.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things, animals etc in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "076ffab5099149dc8c0fca13f59d3b6e"
        }
    ]
}